Register of the Mont Pèlerin Society records
Hoover Institution Archives
- SOUND RECORDINGS, 1956-1966 (Boxes 60-63)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society meeting at Kassel, Germany, 1960 September 6-10 (Boxes 61-63)
    Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern, Wilhelmshöhe 1960. Band Dienstag, 6 September – 11:30-13:00. Uhr. Hunold (organisat. Bemerkhung), Böhm (Chairman), Röpke, Böhm, Leoni, Böhm (organisat. Bemerkhung), Hunold (organisat. Bemerkhung)
    Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern, Wilhelmshöhe 1960. Band Dienstag, 6 September – 17:00-19:00. Uhr. L. von Mises (Chairman), Shaw, Heilperin, Veit, McCord Wright, von Mises, Briefs, Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Hahn, Veit, Shaw, Leoni, Röpke, Erhard (Deutsch), Erhard (translations Grosse Schware), von Mises, Hunold (organisat.Bemerkung)
    Public opinion in a free society. Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern. Band Mittwoch, 7 September 1960 – 9.30-11:00. Uhr. Dr. Hunold (Chairman), Fertig (nicht zu schreiben, da paper verlesen wird), Wesemann, Dr. Hunold, Hoof, Dr. Hunold (organisat. Bemerkung)
    Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern. Band Mittwoch, 7 September 1960 – 11:30-13:00. Uhr. Haberler (Chairman), Dr. Hunold (organis. Bemerkung), Haberler, Schmölders, Haberler, Kuehnelt-Leddihn, D. McCord Wright, Reig, Haberler
    Public opinion in a free society. 7 September 1960 – 17:00-19:00. Prof. Navarro and the linguistics of defending liberalism, the reporter (in French), Ludwig Von Mises on consumers and advertisers, Milton Friedman on the preservation of freedom and the actions of people, question to Professor Friedman, Professor Feaster (sp?) (in German), an unidentified speaker with a German accent, unidentified speaker on inflation and prices, unidentified speaker from the morning session.
    Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern, Wilhelmshöhe 1960. Band Donnerstag, 8 September – 9:30-10:45 Uhr.
    Continued from 7 September: Heilperin, Veit (?), V.Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Chairman Loveday
    8 September: Villey (Chairman), Forster (deutsch), Villey (Zwischenbemerkung), Hunold (Zwischenbemerkung Organisation), Van Sickle (liest sein paper), Duncan, Villey (Zwischenbemerkung), Rougier (nur Anfang)
    Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern, Wilhelmshöhe 1960. Band Donnerstag, 8 September – 10:45-12:30. Uhr. Rougier (Fortsetzung), Villey, Renooij, Villey (Zwischenbemerkungen), translation of Forster (Grosse-Schware), Hunold, Friedman, Röpke, Rustow (deutsch), translation of Rustow, Thurn, Pfister (deutsch), translation of Pfister (Grosse-Schware), v. Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Fredborg, Heilperin, Rustow, translation of Rustow (Grosse-Schware), Stigler, Navarro, Davenport, v. Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Shaw, Zuloaga. All speeches typed.
    8-9 September 1960. The tape begins with an overlap of the end of tape 30, with Navarro as the first speaker heard on tape 31. The rest of this tape (9 September 1960 – 9:30-10:50) concerns economic and financial problems of the West. Leoni serves as chairman. Papers include "Gold Revaluation and Dollar Devaluation" by Albert Hahn of Paris, "Stabilization and the Collective Bargaining Ideal" by Professor Clarence Philbrook of Chapel Hill, and "A New Stage in International Monetary Policy" by Veit from Frankfurt.
    Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern, Wilhelmshöhe 1960. Band Freitag, 9 September – 11:30-13:00. Uhr. Veit (Schluss), Leoni, Haberler (?), coffee break, Dr. Hunold, Chairman (Amerikaner), Loveday (reads his paper), Grantchester, Heilperin, Winterberger, Schwartz, Haberler, Rogge, Thurn, Spat (Anfang)
    9 September 1960 – 17:30-19:00, 21:00-21:40. Includes overlap with part 8. In the additional program, Professor Hayek serves as chairman. The session concerns administrative issues of the society.
    10 September 1960 – 09:30-11:00. Discussing Galbraith’s book. Panelists: Stigler, Hayek, Davenport. Other members respond to the panelists’ ideas.
    Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern, Wilhelmshöhe 1960. Band Samstag, 10 September – 11:30-13:00. Uhr. Hoff, Röpke, Hoff, Heilperin, von Mises on nationalization and socialism, Haberler, Villey, Haberler, Hunold, Villey, Röpke, Schmölders (deutsch), Röpke, Villey (deutsch), Villey (franz.), von Mises, Heilperin, (Deutscher, spricht englisch), Hoff, Röpke (Schlusswort). The common market is also a subject of the talks.
    Sprecherangaben zu den einzelnen Tonbändern der Tagung Wilhelmshöhe 1960. Band "Generalversammlung." Speakers are Hayek, Philbrook, Zwischenbemerkung, Zwischenrufe, Davenport, and Hoff. It is the 10th official, general meeting of the Mont Pelerin Society. It concerns the finances and leadership of the society.
  - Felix Morley speech, "Europe after Suez: An American Viewpoint,", 1957 April (Box 60)
    Use copy reference number: 81123_a_0005543
    Morley speaks about federalism in America, imperialism, and a federated Europe as seen through an outline of American history. Vorlesung 25.
  - Hunold (Albert) recordings of speeches
    - "El renacimiento de la economia de mercado libre,", 1962 (Box 63)
      Use copy reference number: 81123_a_0005629
      A woman speaks in Spanish, including key words such as Mont Pèlerin, Hayek, Röpke, et al.
    - "Auxilio economico: Ruta hacia la libertad o la esclavitud,", 1962 (Box 63)
      Use copy reference number: 81123_a_0005630
      A woman speaks in Spanish.
  - Albert Hunold on the Dr. Nyaradi WLS radio program, 1966 April 17 (Box 63)
    Use copy reference number: 81123_a_0005631
    Fresh from a trip through the continent, Dr. Hunold describes conditions in Africa. He believes there is widespread discontent, with South Africa being an exception. Nyaradi asks him about Chinese and Soviet influence on the continent. He also comments on the influence of the British and Dutch.
  - Albert Hunold on the Dr. Nyaradi WLS radio program, 1966 May 1 (Box 63)
    Use copy reference number: 81123_a_0005632
    Nyaradi interviews Hunold about Switzerland, other European countries, and European integration.
  - Program about Wilhelm Röpke, undated (Box 63)
    Use copy reference number: 81123_a_0005633
    A well produced program, likely about Röpke. In German.
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1947-1980s (Box 64, Photo file)
  Contact prints and 505 prints and postcards depicting mainly members of the Mont Pèlerin Society at various meetings. See also MEETINGS' FILE/Bloemendaal, Netherlands, 1950/Booklets
  - Contact prints depicting members at various meetings, undated (Box-folder 64: 1)
  - 5 unidentified prints, undated (Box-folder 64: 2)
  - 4 prints depicting Albert Hunold's house "Bünishof" in Feldmeilen, Switzerland, undated (Box-folder 64: 3)
  - 14 prints depicting Friedrich A. von Hayek, Carlo Antoni, Karl Brandt, Walter Eucken, and Friedrich A. Lutz in Basel, Switzerland, for the European directors' meeting, 1948 (Box-folder 64: 4)
  - 2 prints depicting a book display at the meeting in St. Moritz, Switzerland, 1957 (Box-folder 64: 5)
  - 13 prints depicting members at the meeting in Oxford, England, 1959 (Box-folder 64: 6)
  - 11 postcards depicting the area around Kassel, Germany, where the 1960 meeting was held (Box-folder 64: 7)
  - 24 prints depicting members attending the meeting in Turin, Italy, and visiting Luigi Einaudi at his home, 1961 (Box-folder 64: 8)
  - 1 print depicting members (including Alvin Rabushka) at the meeting in Madrid, Spain, 1979 (Box-folder 64: 9)
  - 2 prints, one depicting Peter Stanlis, and one depicting Robert E. Hall and Alvin Rabushka, 1980s (Box-folder 64: 10)
  - 2 prints depicting Albert Hunold and others at the first congress of the Association Internationale des Sciences Economiques, Rome, Italy, 1956 September 6-11 (Box-folder 64: 11)
  - 44 prints depicting members at the meeting in Mont Pèlerin, Switzerland,., 1947 (Envelope A)
    See also Envelope J
  - 45 prints and postcards depicting members at the meeting in Bloemendaal, Netherlands, 1950 (Envelope B)
  - 16 prints depicting members at the meeting in Beauvallon, France, 1951 (Envelope C)
  - 19 prints depicting members at the meeting in Seelisberg, Switzerland, 1953 (Envelope D)
  - 16 prints depicting members at the meeting in Venice, Italy, 1954 (Envelope E)
  - 67 prints and postcards depicting members at the meeting in Berlin, Germany, 1956 (Envelope F)
  - 188 prints and postcards depicting members at the meeting in Kassel, Germany, 1960 (Envelope G-H)
  - 18 prints depicting Friedrich A. von Hayek and others at unidentified meetings (Envelope I)
  - 14 prints depicting members at the meeting in Mont Pèlerin, Switzerland, 1947 (Envelope J)
    See also Envelope A
- 2011 INCREMENTAL MATERIALS, 1974-2005 (Boxes 65-138)
  Contains documentation on meetings, membership, financial records, and awards.
  - Mont Pèlerin Society domestic dues listing A-K, 1969-1998 (Box 65)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society domestic dues listing L-Z, 1969-1998 (Box 65)
  - Dues records from Phil Trask, 1974-1968 (Box 65)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society dues listing international, Japan to Venezuela, 1969-1998 (Box 65)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society dues listing international, Argentina to Italy, 1969-1998 (Box 66)
  - Removed and resigned members, 1948-1994 (Box 66)
  - Deceased members, 1969-1997 (Box 66)
  - Removed and resigned members, II, 1980-1996 (Box 66)
  - Membership directories, various years, 1979-1995 (Box 67)
  - Newsletters, various years, 1980-2008 (Box 67)
  - The Future of the Mont Pèlerin Society, 1992-1994 (Box 68)
  - Forms, notices, etcetera, 1982-1994 (Box 68)
  - Action file, 1991-1993 (Box 68)
  - General, 1991 (Box 68)
  - Edwin J. Feulner/Mont Pèlerin Society private file, 1992-1993 (Box 68)
  - F. A. Hayek Fund, 1991 (Box 68)
  - Future meetings, 1979-1989 (Box 68)
  - Summary of aims, 1981-1993 (Box 68)
  - General inquiry letters, 1993-1995 (Box 68)
  - Friedrich von Hayek, 1974 (Box 69)
  - Correspondence, Arthur Kemp, 1979-7980 (Box 69)
  - Correspondence, Max Thurn, 1979-1982 (Box 69)
  - History of the Society, 1983-1992 (Box 69)
  - The History of the Mont Pèlerin by Max Hartwell, 1995 (Box 69)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society history, 1992 (Box 69)
  - Media file, 1992 (Box 69)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 69)
  - Hayek signature, 1978 (Box 69)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society papers, prior to 1974, copies (Box 70)
  - General, prior to 1974 (Box 70)
  - Papers read at Brussels general meeting, 1974 (Box 70)
  - Papers read at Hillsdale, 1975 (Box 70)
  - St. Andrews general meeting, 1976 (Box 70)
  - Authentic Liberal: Compromise, Paris, 1976 (Box 70)
  - Papers read at Paris, 1976 (Box 70)
  - Research for Edwin J. Feulner paper on Compromise, Paris, 1976 (Box 71)
  - Hong Kong general meeting, Sep-79 (Box 71)
  - Hong Kong trip, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Correspondence regarding accounting, 1978-1982 (Box 71)
  - Fund for government investors, 1979-1982 (Box 71)
  - Madison National Bank, 1979 March - 1980 September (Box 71)
  - Directory, 1979 (Box 71)
  - Correspondence, Board members, circa 1979 (Box 71)
  - Correspondence, Manual Ayau, circa 1979 (Box 71)
  - Papers read at Stanford/Hoover, 1980 (Box 72)
  - Printing and advertising costs, 1980 (Box 73)
  - Financial statements, 1980 (Box 73)
  - Contributors, 1980-1982 (Box 73)
  - Correspondence with Lord Harris, circa 1980 (Box 73)
  - Check stubs/transaction register, 1980 August - 1990 March (Box 73)
  - Papers read at Stockholm, 1981 (Box 73)
  - Chile regional meeting, 1981 (Box 73)
  - Financial statements, 1981 (Box 73)
  - Madison National Bank, fiscal year, 1981 March - 1982 March (Box 73)
  - Fellows, Berlin, 1982 (Box 74)
  - Roe Foundation fellowship grant, Berlin, 1982 (Box 74)
  - Fellowships/N. Goto prize, Berlin, 1982 (Box 74)
  - Berlin, general information/planning, 1982 (Box 74)
  - Berlin financials, 1982 (Box 74)
  - Berlin general meeting, 1982 (Box 75)
  - Papers read at Berlin 1982 and Goto winners (Box 75)
  - Taxes and financials, 1982 (Box 75)
  - Financial report and interim statement, 1982-1983 (Box 75)
  - Auditor's reform and tax form, 1982 (Box 75)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Fellows IRS follow up, 1982 (Box 75)
  - Statements, fiscal, 1982-1983 (Box 76)
  - Ledger sheets, 1982-1983 (Box 76)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 76)
  - Papers read at Vancouver, 1983 (Box 76)
  - Expenses, Vancouver, 1983 (Box 76)
  - Vancouver regional meeting, 1983 (Box 76)
  - Vancouver regional meeting, 1983 (Box 76)
  - Tax return, 1983 (Box 77)
  - Donations, 1983-1984 (Box 77)
  - Bank statements, 1983-1984 (Box 77)
  - Membership, 1983 (Box 77)
  - Ledger sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 77)
  - 1984 Cambridge Board meeting (Box 77)
  - Cambridge expenses, 1984 (Box 77)
  - Roe Senior Fellows, Cambridge, 1984 (Box 77)
  - Cambridge 1984 membership updates (Box 77)
  - Cambridge 1984 papers read (Box 77)
  - Cambridge general, 1984 (Box 78)
  - Cambridge 1984 papers read (Box 78)
  - Regional meeting, Paris, 1984 (Box 78)
  - Regional meeting, Paris, papers read, 1984 (Box 78)
  - Financials, 1984 (Box 78)
  - Contributions, 1984-1985 (Box 79)
  - Tax inquiry, 1984 (Box 79)
  - Expenses, 1984-1986 (Box 79)
  - Fellows, IRS follow up, 1984 (Box 79)
  - Bank statements, 1984-1985 (Box 79)
  - Ledger sheets, 1984-1985 (Box 79)
  - Tax status inquiry, 1984 (Box 79)
  - Board meeting, Sydney, 1985 (Box 79)
  - Regional meeting, Australia, 1985 (Box 79)
  - Sydney regional meeting, 1985 (Box 79)
  - Linder Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 80)
  - IRS forms and reports, 1985-1986 (Box 80)
  - Financial reports, tax filing, 1985 (Box 80)
  - Papers read at St. Vincent, 1986 (Box 80)
  - Garvey, St. Vincent, 1986 (Box 80)
  - Goto, St. Vincent, 1986 (Box 80)
  - St. Vincent, 1986 (Box 80)
  - St. Vincent expenses, 1986 (Box 80)
  - St. Vincent Board/travel and hotel, 1986 (Box 80)
  - St. Vincent Board meeting, 1986 (Box 81)
  - Earhart Fellows, 1986 (Box 81)
  - Goto essay competition, 1986 (Box 81)
  - Garvey essay, 1986 (Box 81)
  - Goto competition expenses, 1986 (Box 81)
  - Garvey essay expenses, 1986 (Box 81)
  - St. Vincent, general information, 1986 (Box 81)
  - St. Vincent, 1986 (Box 82)
  - St. Vincent, general invitations, 1986 (Box 82)
  - Edwin J. Feulner, Italy speech, 1986 (Box 82)
  - St. Vincent, general, 1986 (Box 82)
  - Invitations, acceptances and regrets, 1986 (Box 82)
  - Tax returns, financial report, 1986 (Box 82)
  - Donations, 1986-1987 (Box 82)
  - Roe Fellows, 1986 (Box 82)
  - Buchanan meeting, 1986 May 7 (Box 82)
  - Investments, 1986 (Box 82)
  - IRS 1099s, 1986-1987 (Box 82)
  - Statements, fiscal year, 1986-1987 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 83)
  - Comments on "Marketing the Free Market,", 1986 (Box 83)
  - Papers read at Indianapolis, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Indianapolis regional meeting, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Indianapolis, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Projects and expenses, Indianapolis, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Lindner Fund, circa 1987-1988 (Box 84)
  - Fund for Government Investors, circa 1987-1988 (Box 84)
  - Expenses, 1987-1988 (Box 84)
  - Fiscal year, 1987-1988 (Box 84)
  - Madison Bank, 1987-1988 (Box 84)
  - General inquiries, membership, dues, fellowships, 1997-1998 (Box 85)
  - Dues, 1987 (Box 85)
  - Tokyo Bradley Fellows, 1988 (Box 85)
  - Tokyo Earhart Fellows, 1988 (Box 85)
  - Tokyo Roe Fellows, 1988 (Box 85)
  - Tokyo Board meeting, 1988 (Box 85)
  - Tokyo general meeting, proposed guests, 1988 (Box 85)
  - Tokyo general meeting information, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Papers read at Tokyo, 1988 (Box 86)
  - Garvey essay competition, general, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Tokyo Garvey essays I, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Tokyo Garvey essays II, 1988 (Box 87)
  - Taipei special meeting, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Newsletter, 1988-1989 (Box 88)
  - Board of Directors and address update surveys, 1988-1990 (Box 88)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Fiscal year I, 1988-1989 (Box 88)
  - Fiscal year II, 1988-1989 (Box 88)
  - IRS filing, 1988 (Box 88)
  - Dues mailing, 1988 (Box 89)
  - Dues, address changes, etc (Box 89)
  - IRS 1099 filing, 1988 (Box 89)
  - New members, 1988 (Box 89)
  - Board member reimbursement, 1988 (Box 89)
  - New Zealand regional meeting, 1989 (Box 89)
  - Dues I, 1989 (Box 90)
  - Dues II, 1989 (Box 90)
  - Dues III, 1989 (Box 90)
  - Dues IV, 1989 (Box 90)
  - Fiscal year, 1989-1990 (Box 91)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 91)
  - Dues payment, check copies, 1989 (Box 91)
  - Expenses, 1989-1990 (Box 91)
  - Grants and donations, 1989-1992 (Box 91)
  - Munich Board meeting, 1990 (Box 91)
  - Board meeting, Munich, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Roe Fellows, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Garvey essays, 1990 (Box 92)
  - General meeting, Bavaria, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Munich meeting program, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Garvey judges information, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Munich clippings, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Bradley scholars, 1990 (Box 92)
  - Munich meeting guests, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Garvey judging, results notes and correspondence, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Garvey essay competition, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Conference paper, Munich, 1990 (Box 93)
  - Guatemala regional meeting, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Guatemala conference papers, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Hayek Symposium papers, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Earhart Fellows, 1990-1994 (Box 94)
  - Earhart and Bradley Fellows, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Board of Directors address survey, 1990-1992, 1992-1994 (Box 94)
  - IRS filing, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Grants and reports information, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Expenses, 1990-1991 (Box 95)
  - Newsletter 2, 1990 (Box 95)
  - Newsletter 3, 1990 (Box 95)
  - Newsletter 4, 1990 (Box 95)
  - Newsletter, 1990 January (Box 95)
  - Bank statements, 1990-1991 (Box 95)
  - Finances, 1990-1991 (Box 95)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 95)
  - Garvey ads, 1990 (Box 95)
  - Membership and address changes, 1990-1991 (Box 96)
  - Bradley, 1990 (Box 96)
  - Dues I, 1990 (Box 96)
  - Dues II, 1990 (Box 96)
  - Dues III, 1990 (Box 96)
  - Prague meeting, 1991 September (Box 97)
  - Prague meeting, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Prague regional meeting, papers, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Prague regional meeting, expense agreements, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Prague guests, 1991 (Box 97)
  - Prague I, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Prague II, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Prague III, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Prague conference papers, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Big Sky regional meeting, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Newsletter I, 1990 July (Box 99)
  - Newsletter, 1991 October (Box 99)
  - Newsletter 1, 1991 (Box 99)
  - Directory, 1991 (Box 99)
  - Dues correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
  - Expenses, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
  - Bank statements, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
  - Board member reimbursements, 1991 (Box 99)
  - Bank correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
  - Checks received, copies, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
  - Correspondence I, 1991 (Box 100)
  - Correspondence II, 1991 (Box 100)
  - Vancouver meeting, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Board meeting minutes, Vancouver, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Vancouver general meeting, guests, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Vancouver meeting letters, miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Vancouver general meeting, expenses, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Bradley Fellows, Vancouver, 1992 (Box 101)
  - Vancouver general meeting, 1992 (Box 101)
  - General meeting Vancouver, conference papers I, 1992 (Box 101)
  - General meeting Vancouver, conference papers II, 1992 (Box 101)
  - Liberty Fund Conference on History of the Mont Pèlerin Society, 1992 August (Box 102)
  - Liberty Fund Conference on History of the Mont Pèlerin Society expenses, 1992 August (Box 102)
  - Expenses, 1992-1993 (Box 102)
  - Garvey procedure sheet request, 1992 (Box 102)
  - Financials and IRS, 1992 (Box 102)
  - Roe Fellows, 1992-1993 (Box 102)
  - IRS filing and audit, 1992-1993 (Box 102)
  - Correspondence, 1992 January-June (Box 103)
  - Correspondence, 1992 July-December (Box 103)
  - Contributions, 1992-1993 (Box 103)
  - Bank statements, fiscal year, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Grant reports information, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Garvey advertisement, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Future of the Mont Pèlerin Society committee file, Chairman Manuel Ayau, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Earhart Fellows, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Newsletter Vol. 45, #2, Hayek tribute (Box 103)
  - Correspondence, additional, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Brazil regional meeting, 1993 (Box 103)
  - Brazil regional meeting, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Brazil regional meeting, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Brazil regional meeting, guest file, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Rio conference material, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Checks received, copies, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Directory, circa 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - Delinquent members, 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - Action file, circa 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - Newsletter, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Newsletter, Vol. 46, #1, 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - Newsletter, 1993 December (Box 105)
  - Contributions, 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - Expenses, 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - IRS material, circa 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - Action file, 1993 August (Box 106)
  - Bank statements, 1993-1994 (Box 106)
  - Bank statements, 1993-1994 (Box 106)
  - Finances, 1993-1994 (Box 106)
  - Freidrich A. von Hayek Fellowship contest letters, 1993-1994 (Box 106)
  - Special Board meeting, Washington DC, 1994 December 17-19 (Box 106)
  - Hotel/meeting planning, special meeting, Washington DC, 1994 December 17-19 (Box 106)
  - Special Board meeting, Washington DC, 1994 December 17-19 (Box 107)
  - Symposium papers, Cannes, 1994 (Box 107)
  - Papers from Cannes general meeting, 1994 (Box 107)
  - Special Board meeting, Washington DC, 1994 December 17-19 (Box 107)
  - Earhart Fellows, Cannes, France, 1994 (Box 108)
  - Cannes, France I, 1994 September 25-30 (Box 108)
  - Cannes, France II, 1994 September 25-30 (Box 108)
  - Cannes, France general, 1994 (Box 108)
  - Hayek Fellows, Cannes, France, 1994 (Box 108)
  - Accounting/reimbursements, Cannes, 1994 (Box 108)
  - B. Travers, Cannes, France, 1994 (Box 108)
  - Roe Fellows, Cannes, 1994 (Box 108)
  - Bradley Fellows, Cannes, 1994 (Box 109)
  - Cannes I, 1994 (Box 109)
  - Cannes II, 1994 (Box 109)
  - Cannes III, 1994 (Box 109)
  - Hayek contest letters, Cannes, 1994 (Box 110)
  - Hayek essay contest I, 1994 (Box 110)
  - Hayek essay contest II, 1994 (Box 110)
  - International dues notices, 1995 (Box 111)
  - Domestic dues notices, 1995 (Box 111)
  - Contributions, 1994-1995 (Box 112)
  - IRS filing and audit, 1994-1995 (Box 112)
  - Checks received, copies, 1994 (Box 112)
  - Sequoia National Bank, 1994 (Box 112)
  - F. A. Hayek Fellowship, 1994 (Box 112)
  - Membership changes since Vancouver, 1992-1994 (Box 112)
  - Nominations for future members, 1994 (Box 112)
  - Investments, 1994-1995 (Box 112)
  - Accounts, 1994 (Box 112)
  - Action file, 1994 (Box 112)
  - Personal/confidential, 1994 (Box 112)
  - Regional meeting Cape Town I, 1995 September 10-13 (Box 113)
  - Regional meeting Cape Town II, 1995 September 10-13 (Box 113)
  - Cape Town conference materials, 1995 (Box 113)
  - Proceedings and newsletter, 1995 (Box 113)
  - Various reimbursement accounts, Cape Town, 1995 (Box 113)
  - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 114)
  - Visa/Mastercard application, National Capital Bank of Washington, 1995 (Box 114)
  - National Review article, 1995 (Box 114)
  - Expenses, 1995-1996 (Box 114)
  - Checks received, copies, 1995 (Box 114)
  - General correspondence, 1995 January-April (Box 114)
  - General correspondence, 1995 May-July (Box 114)
  - General correspondence, 1995 August-December (Box 114)
  - Sequoia Bank statements, 1995 (Box 114)
  - Matercard dues payment, 1995-1996 (Box 115)
  - Visa credit card dues payment, 1995-1996 (Box 115)
  - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 115)
  - General meeting, Vienna Austria, 1996 September 9-13 (Box 115)
  - Hayek essays, winners/honorable mentions, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Fellowship response, Vienna, 1996 (Box 115)
  - The Roe Foundation, Vienna, Austria, 1995-1996 (Box 115)
  - Earhart Fellowships, Vienna, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Atlas Foundation Fellows, Vienna, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Olin Fellows, Vienna, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Hayek Fellows, Aequus Institute grant, Vienna, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Carthage Fellows, 1996 (Box 116)
  - Vienna Board meetings, 1996 (Box 116)